<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Companies on UBC Technical Career Fair</title>
    <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Companies on UBC Technical Career Fair</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ubctcf.com/companies/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A Thinking Ape</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/a-thinking-ape/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/a-thinking-ape/</guid>
      <description>A Thinking Ape is a small yet driven team that is dedicated to building strong mobile communities.
With our collaborative approach to product design, we ensure the best ideas get the space they need to grow.
Our team seeks out intuitive solutions to complex problems, and maintains strong ties to our hacker culture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AppNeta</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/appneta/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/appneta/</guid>
      <description>AppNeta is the leader in proactive end-user performance monitoring solutions built for the distributed enterprise. With AppNeta, IT and Network Ops teams can assure continual and exceptional delivery of business-critical applications. AppNeta&amp;rsquo;s SaaS-based solutions give IT teams essential application and network performance data, allowing them to continuously monitor user experience across any application, network, data center or cloud.
At AppNeta, we take application and network performance seriously without taking ourselves too seriously.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aquatic Informatics</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/aquatic-infomatics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/aquatic-infomatics/</guid>
      <description>Aquatic Informatics™ provides leading software solutions that address critical water data management and analysis challenges for the rapidly growing environmental monitoring industry. Aquatic Informatics is the trusted provider of hydrologic management solutions to hundreds of federal, state/provincial and local government departments, hydropower operators, mining companies, academic groups, and consulting organizations around the world, who collect, manage, and process large volumes of water quality or quantity data.
Aquatic Informatics has earned a global reputation for innovation in environmental data management.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arista Networks</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/arista-networks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/arista-networks/</guid>
      <description>Arista Networks was founded to deliver cloud networking solutions for large data center and computing environments. Arista offers a broad portfolio of Gigabit Ethernet solutions including 1,10 and 40 GbE switches that redefine network architectures, bring extensibility to networking and dramatically change the price/performance of data center networks. At the core of Arista&amp;rsquo;s platform is EOS (Extensible Operating System), the world&amp;rsquo;s most advanced network operating system, designed to build software defined cloud networks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Avigilon</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/avigilon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/avigilon/</guid>
      <description>Pronunciation: a-vigil-on Definition: To be perpetually alert and watchful
Avigilon designs, develops, and manufactures video analytics, network video management software and hardware, surveillance cameras, and access control solutions. Avigilon&amp;rsquo;s solutions have been installed at thousands of customer sites, including school campuses, transportation systems, healthcare centers, public venues, critical infrastructure, prisons, factories, casinos, airports, financial institutions, government facilities, and retailer</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Benevity Inc.</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/benevity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/benevity/</guid>
      <description>Better Work and a Better World: at Benevity that’s what we’re all about. We’re a software company in the business of doing good, building better ways for companies to connect with their customers and employees around causes (we make “doing well by doing good” more than just a tagline!). We’re growing fast and looking for more great people to join us.
We’re not Bono, just a passionate crew of workhorses out to change the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Buy Canada</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/best-buy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/best-buy/</guid>
      <description>Best Buy Canada is one of the largest omni-channel retailers of consumer electronics, computers and entertainment products, related accessories and services in Canada.
Our Canadian Corporate Head Quarters is 140,000 square feet, two stories high and is designed as an open office environment where teamwork is encouraged. Being located in Burnaby B.C. offers a great lifestyle living on the West Coast of Canada. With great food and Starbucks coffee made available in our subsidized cafeteria, a full fitness center on-site, a nearby outdoor park with running paths along the scenic Fraser River, free shuttle and parking, and much more, the energy of Best Buy Canada, Ltd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BGC Engineering</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/bgc-engineering/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/bgc-engineering/</guid>
      <description>BGC Engineering Inc. is an international consulting firm providing engineering and geoscience services to the mining, energy, and transportation industries over the last 27 years. We offer you the potential to work on the world&amp;rsquo;s most recognizable client projects with world class technical experts in applied earth sciences complimented with a strong focus on career development, while also promoting a social environment that encourages a healthy work-life balance. BGC is a growing team of over 400 people working in a unique employee-owned company with a flat management structure that emphasizes teamwork and shared leadership at all levels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clio</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/clio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/clio/</guid>
      <description>Clio is the most comprehensive cloud-based practice management platform for the legal industry. With the help of the cloud, Clio eases the process of time tracking, billing, administration, and collaboration for law firms of all sizes. Based in Vancouver, B.C. and launched in 2008, Clio is used by legal professionals in over 50 countries. Clio has raised $27 million from investors including Bessemer Venture Partners. Learn more at www.clio.com.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Copperleaf Technologies</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/copperleaf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/copperleaf/</guid>
      <description>Building a better world one decision at a time. Copperleaf provides Decision Analytics to companies facing the challenges of managing critical infrastructure. Our enterprise software solutions leverage operational and financial data to help our clients make investment decisions that deliver the highest value to their stakeholders. Copperleaf’s dynamic risk and value framework, predictive analytics, state-of-the-art optimization, and interactive visualizations empower businesses to make complex investment decisions with confidence. In 2016, Canadian Business Magazine named Copperleaf as one of the top 20 fastest-growing software companies in Canada.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>D2L Corporation</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/d2l-corporation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/d2l-corporation/</guid>
      <description>D2L was founded in 1999 by John Baker. At the time, his engineering class was being challenged to look at the world in new ways by coming up with questions that no one had asked before.
John realized that despite all the change technology was driving in the world, his University campus seemed almost untouched by that momentum. The question he wanted to ask was clear: how could we use technology to dramatically transform learning?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dapper Labs (Axiom Zen)</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/axiom-zen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/axiom-zen/</guid>
      <description>Axiom Zen is the venture studio behind several successful startups including Dapper Labs (the makers of CryptoKitties), ZenHub (the world&amp;rsquo;s leading developer-focused project management platform), Routific (the world&amp;rsquo;s leading route optimization engine), and many others. Formed in February 2018, Dapper Labs was spun out of Axiom Zen to spread the benefits of decentralization through the power of play, fairness, and true ownership.
Axioms are humble and curious entrepreneurs, builders, and tinkerers who share a passion to demystify blockchain technology and tap its potential to create change in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FDM Group</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/fdm-group/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/fdm-group/</guid>
      <description>FDM Group is a global professional services provider with a focus on IT. With over 180 clients worldwide and over 3000 IT and business consultants, FDM brings people and technology together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FI.SPAN</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/fi-span/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/fi-span/</guid>
      <description>FI.SPAN enables banks to provide bank branded ERP connectors and adapters to their most valuable commercial clients.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finger Food Studios</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/finger-food-studios/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/finger-food-studios/</guid>
      <description>Finger Food is a world-class technology company that designs and develops immersive Mobile, MR/AR/VR, Internet of Things, Machine Learning, Cloud and Entertainment products. Our work transforms industries. We are passionate about embracing and innovating bleeding-edge technological opportunities and delivering products that achieve tangible ROI in real-world scenarios.
We work with iOS, Android, Microsoft HoloLens, Tango, Oculus, HTC Vive, and Unity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fortinet Technologies</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/fortinet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/fortinet/</guid>
      <description>Fortinet is a global leader in providing Cyber security solutions. We develop next generation firewall systems and high end Security Systems like Fortigate, FortiSandbox, FortiAnalyzer, Forticlient and many other products to enterprise security to our clients which also includes Fortune 100 companies. Our flagship enterprise firewall platform, FortiGate, is available in a wide range of sizes and form factors to fit any environment, and provides a broad array of next generation security and networking functions covering Network security, Data center security (physical and virtual), Cloud security, Secure (wired and wireless) access, Infrastructure (switching and routing) security, Content security, Endpoint security, Application Security.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GeoGuard</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/geoguard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/geoguard/</guid>
      <description>A clear market-leader in cyber-security, GeoGuard specializes in fighting and detecting location fraud protecting regulated the industries as well as the global film, TV &amp;amp; sports world.
Working with some of the best known brands on the planet, GeoGuard delivers mission-critical solutions on a platform agnostic basis, across 200 million unique devices worldwide.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Global Relay</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/global-relay/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/global-relay/</guid>
      <description>Global Relay is the leading provider of cloud-based electronic message archiving, supervision, and eDiscovery solutions for the global financial sector, delivering services to 20,000 customers in 90 countries, including 22 of the world’s top 25 banks. Global Relay Archive securely captures and preserves email, instant messaging, mobile messaging, Bloomberg, Thomson Reuters, Twitter, LinkedIn, Facebook and more — with Blackberry, iPhone, iPad, Android, Outlook and Web access.
Apply today – we have five floors of great open space offices with a fast-paced vibe, lots of amenities, a roof top deck &amp;amp; BBQ, and an in-house chef, all located in the heart of Gastown near Waterfront Station.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ICBC</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/icbc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/icbc/</guid>
      <description>A career at ICBC is an opportunity to be part of a talented, diverse and inclusive team that is driven to serve its customers and community. Make the most of your skills and take the opportunity to grow and develop your career. You can expect a competitive salary, comprehensive benefits and a challenging work environment. Drive your career with us.
ICBC is committed to being an inclusive employer, one that reflects the diversity of the people and communities of British Columbia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JOMAR Softcorp Services Inc.</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/jomar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/jomar/</guid>
      <description>JOMAR integrates &amp;lsquo;Next Generation IT&amp;rsquo; with the software development of our ERP Suite for Vertical Industry Sectors, Smart Grid Utility Systems, and insurance Applications based on a common architecture for implementation on multi-platform servers and deployment to the private Cloud on JOMAR Hosting Services in PEER1 locations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Motion Metrics International</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/motion-metrics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/motion-metrics/</guid>
      <description>With over fifteen years of experience, Motion Metrics applies the latest in artificial intelligence and deep learning techniques to solve tough safety and efficiency related challenges in mines, quarries, and industrial sites around the world. As a growing company, we are always searching for new talent with a passion for developing cutting-edge technology. Motion Metrics is looking for engineers, developers, and computer scientists from all disciplines and backgrounds to join our diverse team at our headquarters in Vancouver, BC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NetApp</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/netapp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/netapp/</guid>
      <description>Leading organizations worldwide count on NetApp for software, systems and services to manage and store their data. Customers value our teamwork, expertise and passion for helping them succeed now and into the future.
Creating a model company is at the heart of everything we do. This means delivering value to each community we serve: customers, shareholders, employees, partners, and neighbors.
We are committed to living our core values: • Trust and Integrity • Leadership • Simplicity • Adaptability • Teamwork • Go Beyond • Get Things Done The strength of our culture means that we attract the industry’s best to work for our customers’ success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Orbis</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/orbis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/orbis/</guid>
      <description>Orbis is a privately-held global investment management firm that invests over $25 billion in capital. The firm manages several performance-driven equity funds in both long-only and absolute return strategies using a long-term, fundamental, contrarian investment approach. Orbis employs approximately 400 people in eight countries, who represent more than 35 nationalities, speak more than 15 languages and come from a wide range of educational and professional backgrounds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PDFTron Systems Inc.</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/pdftron/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/pdftron/</guid>
      <description>PDFTron Systems Inc. is a premier provider of standards-based document technologies related to PDF, XPS, SVG, ePub, MS Office, HTML, and other graphic file formats. PDFTron&amp;rsquo;s cross-platform, high-performance developer components power well-known commercial products, complex enterprise-wide document management and publishing workflows, as well as high-traffic web-based applications, changing how we use documents one application at a time in virtually all industry areas.
PDFTron fosters an atmosphere of opportunity, growth, and success for every single individual amidst an exciting, challenging and entrepreneurial culture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ping Identity</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/ping-identity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/ping-identity/</guid>
      <description>Our mission is to simplify how enterprises provide secure and seamless digital experiences. For the world’s largest organizations, we help prevent security breaches, increase employee and partner productivity and provide personalized customer experiences. Enterprises choose Ping for our identity expertise, open standards leadership, partnership with companies like Microsoft, Amazon and Google, and collaboration with customers like Boeing, Cisco, Disney, GE, Kraft Foods, Walgreens and over half of the Fortune 100.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Qumulo</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/qumulo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/qumulo/</guid>
      <description>At Qumulo we&amp;rsquo;ve built a truly unique distributed file system from scratch. It wasn&amp;rsquo;t easy and it&amp;rsquo;s far from a finished product. Joining Qumulo&amp;rsquo;s team of elite engineers means working on an innovative product at its infancy and watching your work take effect. It&amp;rsquo;s an opportunity to work directly with customers and increase the value of our product by solving their most challenging problems.
We hire smart, adaptive engineers with diverse backgrounds and a knack for taking challenges head on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Realtor.com</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/realtor-com/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/realtor-com/</guid>
      <description>Realtor.com®, operated by Move, Inc., is the fastest growing online real estate destination for homebuyers, sellers and renters. Today, with over 3 million listings from nearly 800 multiple listing services (MLS), we have the most homes for sale nationwide than any competing real estate marketplaces.
At realtor.com®, we’re on a mission to give people everywhere the power to discover their next dream home, from anywhere. We’re building world-class real estate solutions that empower realtors with the tools, knowledge and confidence they need to connect people with their perfect home to grow their business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SAP</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/sap/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/sap/</guid>
      <description>SAP is the world’s leading provider of enterprise applications, cloud services, analytics, mobile, and database. SAP helps organizations fight the damaging effects of complexity, generate new opportunities for innovation and growth, and stay ahead of the competition.
From back office to boardroom, warehouse to storefront, desktop to mobile device, SAP empowers people and organizations to work together more efficiently and use business insight more effectively to stay ahead of the competition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tableau</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/tableau/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/tableau/</guid>
      <description>Tableau Software is an American computer software company headquartered in Seattle, Washington. It produces a family of interactive data visualization products focused on business intelligence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TELUS</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/telus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/telus/</guid>
      <description>TELUS&amp;rsquo; Graduate Technology Leadership Program (GTLP) is a one-of-a-kind technical development program with a focus on technology and innovation. Through a series of rotations, the program will expose you to a breadth of functions to build your technical skills while you deliver on the technology needs of our customers. You will complete three 9-12 month rotations choosing from five technology streams. Streams include Security, SDN / NFV, Wireless, Future Friendly Home Services, and Software Design.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teradici</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/teradici/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/teradici/</guid>
      <description>Teradici is the creator of the PCoIP remoting protocol technology and Cloud Access Software, the leading solution for a cloud-ready future. Founded in 2004, the Burnaby company is focused on its core mission of seamless delivery of workstations and applications for end-users.
Teradici PCoIP® technology is the most secure remoting technology in the marketplace, enabling visualization of even the most graphics-intensive applications. Teradici Cloud Access Software, built on PCoIP technology, enables enterprises to securely leverage public cloud GPU instances to confidently lift and shift the most graphics-intensive Windows or Linux applications to the public cloud, avoiding costly rewrites.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TTT Studios</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/ttt-studios/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/ttt-studios/</guid>
      <description>TTT Studio is a world-class software development Company working for a global client list in multiple industries. Over the past 9 years, we have built multiple applications and patented a portfolio of technologies. This experience puts us in the best position to cater larger accounts and launch our own products.
We are a family. We have fun. Design means everything to us and we have the technical chops to deliver what lesser programmers might describe as spooky magic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visier</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/visier/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/visier/</guid>
      <description>A leading innovator in Applied Big Data cloud technology, Visier provides Workforce Intelligence solutions that are enabling a rapidly growing number of the world&amp;rsquo;s best brands to maximize their business outcomes through their people.
Visier&amp;rsquo;s solutions let organizations understand and plan - with precision - how to best and most cost-effectively recruit, retain, and develop their workforce. With Visier, senior leaders, HR, and people managers alike can answer key workforce questions, align on goals and strategies, and act on decisions and plans to drive improved business outcomes.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>