<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Companies on UBC Technical Career Fair</title>
    <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Companies on UBC Technical Career Fair</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ubctcf.com/companies/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A Thinking Ape Entertainment Ltd</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/a-thinking-ape-entertainment-ltd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/a-thinking-ape-entertainment-ltd/</guid>
      <description>Overview &amp;ldquo;Surrounded by mountains and water in beautiful Vancouver, BC, we are smart people who like smart people. We create mobile games with a social core that engage players and provoke us with creative new problems.
When we set out to make great games with massive online communities, we knew that we first had to create the ideal environment for building ambitious things. A place where brilliant and inspiring people could come together and build games that make millions of players happy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AbCellera</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/abcellera/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/abcellera/</guid>
      <description>Overview &amp;ldquo;At AbCellera, you won&amp;rsquo;t just be redesigning another website or creating a copy-and-paste app experience. We know you&amp;rsquo;ve done that all before.
Here, we&amp;rsquo;re solving tough problems and creating innovative solutions from the ground up - complex data visualization &amp;amp; analysis tools that leverage machine learning from rich data sets to revolutionize the way that scientists explore antibodies. This is life-changing research, and you could be a part of it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Absolute Software</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/absolute-software/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/absolute-software/</guid>
      <description>Overview &amp;ldquo;Absolute provides persistent endpoint security and data risk management solutions for computers, tablets and smartphones. Our customers rely on us to provide them with a unique and trusted layer of security so they can manage mobility while remaining firmly in control. Our Persistence technology is embedded into the core of most devices at the factory. Once activated, it provides you with comprehensive visibility into all of your devices enabling you to confidently manage mobility, investigate potential threats and take action if a security incident occurs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazon</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/amazon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/amazon/</guid>
      <description>Overview &amp;ldquo;At Amazon, our evolution has been driven by the spirit of innovation that is part of our DNA. As a new college graduate or intern, you can have multiple opportunities to innovate and solve real-world, complex technical and business problems as you join us on our journey.
We strive to hire the brightest minds from universities around the globe, and have various career opportunities available for undergraduates and advanced degree students with diverse academic backgrounds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AppNeta</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/appneta/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/appneta/</guid>
      <description>Overview &amp;ldquo;AppNeta provides proactive end user performance monitoring solutions for your business critical applications over any network. Using AppNeta, IT and Network Operations teams have access to essential performance data to monitor and measure the performance of their web, mobile and cloud-delivered application environments. AppNeta&amp;rsquo;s unique and patented TruPath technology eschews traditional device-centric measurement techniques and instead measures performance along the actual application path, allowing AppNeta to measure application performance across both public and private networks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aquatic Informatics</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/aquatic-informatics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/aquatic-informatics/</guid>
      <description>Overview &amp;ldquo;Aquatic Informatics provides software solutions that address critical water data management, analytics, and compliance challenges for the rapidly growing water industry. Water monitoring agencies worldwide trust Aquatic Informatics to acquire, process, model, and publish water information in real time. We offer a full range of solutions, from standalone software packages for individual users, hosted software services, and enterprise-wide national systems serving thousands of users and processing environmental data from several thousand monitoring stations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arista Networks</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/arista-networks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/arista-networks/</guid>
      <description>Overview &amp;ldquo;Arista Networks is a leader in building scalable, high-performance and ultra-low latency cloud networks with low power consumption and a small footprint for modern datacenter and campus environments. Arista has shipped more than 20 million cloud networking ports worldwide with CloudVision and EOS, an advanced network operating system.
Arista&amp;rsquo;s hardware platforms are designed to meet the stringent power and cooling requirements of today&amp;rsquo;s most demanding data centers, proven advantages already in use in many of the largest cloud data centers around the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Asana</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/asana/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/asana/</guid>
      <description>Overview &amp;ldquo;At Asana, we&amp;rsquo;re building a place where teams align their energies towards common goals. Where there is no work about work. There is only total clarity, energized focus, and frictionless collaboration. Everything from the most immediate details to the big picture are organized and at your fingertips. In every moment, each person knows what they should be doing and why they&amp;rsquo;re doing it.&amp;rdquo; What are the skills and qualities of a successful candidate in your organization?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Avigilon</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/avigilon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/avigilon/</guid>
      <description>Overview &amp;ldquo;At Avigilon we are helping solve some of the biggest challenges around safety and physical security by developing advanced artificial intelligence (AI) technologies and products that are used to help keep people, businesses, and cities around the world safer. Avigilon, a Motorola Solutions company, designs, develops, and manufactures advanced AI, video analytics, network video management software and hardware, surveillance cameras, and access control solutions that help change the way people interact with their security systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Axiom Zen</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/axiom-zen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/axiom-zen/</guid>
      <description>Overview &amp;ldquo;Axiom Zen is a startup that builds startups. Founded in 2013, we have built dozens of products and four standalone companies that serve hundreds of millions of consumers. Our companies include Dapper Labs (the makers of CryptoKitties, the world&amp;rsquo;s most popular blockchain game), ZenHub (improving developer productivity in startups and Fortune 500 companies), and Routific (a leading route optimization platform). Axiom Zen was named first among Canada&amp;rsquo;s Most Innovative Companies in 2016.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BC Pension Corporation</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/bc-pension-corporation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/bc-pension-corporation/</guid>
      <description>Overview &amp;ldquo;BC Pension Corporation is one of the largest professional pension services organizations in Canada. Doing meaningful work and with a challenging mandate, we provide comprehensive pension services to five BC public sector pension plans. In addition, the corporation is executing on a forward-thinking, transformational strategy that will change the way we serve plan members and employers. Our strategic plan, From 12 to 21, is an ambitious program of business transformation that supports high service levels and cost-effective delivery through better use of technology, improved business process and continued attention to staff training and development.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Benevity Inc.</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/benevity-inc./</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/benevity-inc./</guid>
      <description>Overview &amp;ldquo;Better Work and a Better World: at Benevity that&amp;rsquo;s what we&amp;rsquo;re all about. We&amp;rsquo;re a software company in the business of doing good, building better ways for companies to connect with their customers and employees around causes (we make &amp;ldquo;&amp;ldquo;doing well by doing good&amp;rdquo;&amp;rdquo; more than just a tagline!). We&amp;rsquo;re growing fast and looking for more great people to join us.
We&amp;rsquo;re not Bono, just a passionate crew of workhorses out to change the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BGC Engineering Inc.</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/bgc-engineering-inc./</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/bgc-engineering-inc./</guid>
      <description>Overview &amp;ldquo;BGC Engineering Inc. is an international consulting firm providing engineering and geoscience services to the mining, energy, and transportation industries over the last 27 years. We offer you the potential to work on the world&amp;rsquo;s most recognizable client projects with world class technical experts in applied earth sciences complimented with a strong focus on career development, while also promoting a social environment that encourages a healthy work-life balance. BGC is a growing team of over 400 people working in a unique employee-owned company with a flat management structure that emphasizes teamwork and shared leadership at all levels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>British Columbia Investment Management Corporation</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/british-columbia-investment-management-corporation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/british-columbia-investment-management-corporation/</guid>
      <description>Overview &amp;ldquo;With $153.4 billion of managed assets, British Columbia Investment Management Corporation (BCI) is a leading provider of investment management services for British Columbia&amp;rsquo;s public sector and one of the largest asset managers in Canada. BCI seeks investment opportunities around the world and across a range of asset classes that convert savings into productive capital. Our investment returns play a significant role in helping our institutional clients build a financially secure future for their beneficiaries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Broadridge</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/broadridge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/broadridge/</guid>
      <description>Overview &amp;ldquo;Broadridge, a global fintech leader with over $4 billion in revenue, provides communications, technology, data, and analytics. We help drive business transformation for our clients with solutions for enriching client engagement, navigating risk, optimizing efficiency, and generating revenue growth. Broadridge employs over 10,000 full-time associates globally with a significant presence in North America, Europe, and Asia.&amp;rdquo; What are the skills and qualities of a successful candidate in your organization? &amp;ldquo;Experience designing and developing business intelligence applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brock Solutions</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/brock-solutions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/brock-solutions/</guid>
      <description>Overview &amp;ldquo;Brock Solutions is an engineering solutions and professional services company that forges lasting relationships with customers globally to implement real-time operational solutions, as measured by the success of our customers, through a growing, networked organization that deploys passionate, innovative teams.
Brock is a leader in the industrial engineering solution space, specializing in software development and controls automation all around the world.
Developing leading advanced solutions first depends on developing a great team of people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Burli Software Inc.</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/burli-software-inc./</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/burli-software-inc./</guid>
      <description>Overview &amp;ldquo;Burli Software is a Vancouver-based software company that has been developing, selling and supporting software for the broadcast industry for more than 20 years. Its key products, which are used worldwide by thousands of professional journalists, are applications for managing content (text, audio, video) for radio and television newsrooms.&amp;rdquo; What are the skills and qualities of a successful candidate in your organization? &amp;ldquo;Excellent verbal and written communication skills, team player, strong understanding of computer science fundamentals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clio</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/clio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/clio/</guid>
      <description>Overview &amp;ldquo;Cloud-based practice management software for legal professionals. We work to transform the practice of law, for good!&amp;rdquo; What are the skills and qualities of a successful candidate in your organization? &amp;ldquo;You&amp;rsquo;ve completed your second year coursework and are a 3rd or 4th year Computer Science/Engineering student; You are a rational and critical thinker who seeks solutions when you find problems; Excellent computer science fundamentals: data structures, algorithms; programming languages, SQL; Superb communication skills written, verbal, and spoken.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Communications security establishment</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/communications-security-establishment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/communications-security-establishment/</guid>
      <description>Overview &amp;ldquo;CSE is one of Canada&amp;rsquo;s key security and intelligence organizations, focussed on collecting foreign signals intelligence in support of the Government of Canada&amp;rsquo;s priorities, and on helping protect the computer networks and information of greatest importance to Canada. Do you want to directly contribute to maintaining the safety and prosperity of Canada? To work with some of the most advanced technologies in the world? Imagine yourself working for an organization where you can explore a variety of new experiences, new ways of working&amp;hellip; and make a real difference.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Copperleaf Technologies</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/copperleaf-technologies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/copperleaf-technologies/</guid>
      <description>Overview &amp;ldquo;Building a better world one decision at a time. Copperleaf provides Decision Analytics to companies facing the challenges of managing critical infrastructure. Our enterprise software solutions leverage operational and financial data to help our clients make investment decisions that deliver the highest value to their stakeholders. Copperleaf&amp;rsquo;s dynamic risk and value framework, predictive analytics, state-of-the-art optimization, and interactive visualizations empower businesses to make complex investment decisions with confidence. Headquartered in Vancouver, our solutions are distributed and supported by regional staff and partners worldwide.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coursera</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/coursera/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/coursera/</guid>
      <description>Overview &amp;ldquo;Coursera was founded by two computer science professors at Stanford with a vision of providing life-transforming learning experiences to anyone, anywhere. It is the world&amp;rsquo;s largest online learning platform for higher education. 190 of the world&amp;rsquo;s top universities and industry educators partner with Coursera to offer courses, Specializations, and degrees that empower over 45 million learners around the world to achieve their career goals. Over 1,800 companies use the company&amp;rsquo;s enterprise platform Coursera for Business to transform their talent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>D2L Corporation</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/d2l-corporation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/d2l-corporation/</guid>
      <description>Overview &amp;ldquo;We are the creators of Brightspace, the world&amp;rsquo;s first truly integrated learning platform. We partner with thought-leading organizations around the globe to improve learning through data-driven technology that helps deliver a personalized experience to every learner, regardless of geography or ability. Our platform is used by more than 1,100 clients and 15 million learners in higher education, K-12, healthcare, government, and the enterprise sector.
Fifteen years after the company was formed, our team has grown to include over 800 employees and offices in several countries around the world, including the United States, Canada, Europe, Australia, Brazil, and Singapore.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Delta Controls Inc.</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/delta-controls-inc./</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/delta-controls-inc./</guid>
      <description>Overview &amp;ldquo;Delta Controls is one of the largest independent manufacturers of building automation systems with more than 300 installers in over 80 countries. For more than 3 decades Delta Controls has offered dependable and user-friendly building control solutions to commercial, healthcare, education, leisure buildings and more. As industry leaders, our track record includes delivering the world&amp;rsquo;s first fully integrated native BACnet building solution encompassing HVAC, Lighting and Access products.&amp;rdquo; What are the skills and qualities of a successful candidate in your organization?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DNEG</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/dneg/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/dneg/</guid>
      <description>Overview &amp;ldquo;We are DNEG, one of the world&amp;rsquo;s leading visual effects, animation and stereo conversion companies for feature film and television, with studios in London, Vancouver, Mumbai, Los Angeles, Chennai, Montr�al, Chandigarh, Hyderabad and Goa.&amp;rdquo; What are the skills and qualities of a successful candidate in your organization? &amp;ldquo;You will have: - Solid understanding of computer graphics and mathematics - Knowledge of Python and C++ - Good written and verbal communication skills - Desire to work collaboratively with others and enjoy working in a team environment</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EY - Client Technology</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/ey-client-technology/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/ey-client-technology/</guid>
      <description>Overview &amp;ldquo;EY&amp;rsquo;s people in more than 170 countries are committed to operating with integrity, quality, and professionalism in the provision of audit, tax, transaction, and advisory services. We strive to help all of our people achieve their professional and personal goals through an inclusive environment that values everyone&amp;rsquo;s contributions, appreciates diversity of thought, fosters growth, and provides continuous opportunities for development. Recognized as one of Canada&amp;rsquo;s top employers, EY continually strives to be a great place to work&amp;rdquo; What are the skills and qualities of a successful candidate in your organization?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FDM Group Canada Inc</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/fdm-group-canada-inc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/fdm-group-canada-inc/</guid>
      <description>Overview &amp;ldquo;FDM Group is an international IT services provider located across the globe in North America, Europe, and Asia-Pacific. FDM&amp;rsquo;s business model provides opportunities for recent graduates and young IT professionals to kick-start their careers as IT and Business Consultants. We are renowned for our Academy Program equipping graduates with award-winning business and technical training in core disciplines prior to working on client sites as FDM Consultants for two years where they can gain practical commercial experience with our diverse client range and help to achieve specific business objectives within various sectors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finger Food Advanced Technology Group</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/finger-food-advanced-technology-group/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/finger-food-advanced-technology-group/</guid>
      <description>Overview &amp;ldquo;Using the latest technology including Mixed Reality, Augmented Reality and Virtual Reality, AI, Machine Learning, and the Internet of Things, Finger Food works across platforms to provide innovative, industry-first solutions for global companies. We have a passion for building partnerships with our clients, and we have a reputation for outstanding delivery.
Founded in 2009, Finger Food is led by CEO Ryan Peterson in the beautiful Tri-Cities area of BC. Finger Food harnesses the talents of a diverse and dedicated team of fearless innovators.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FISPAN Services Inc.</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/fispan-services-inc./</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/fispan-services-inc./</guid>
      <description>Overview FISPAN enables banks to provide bank branded ERP connectors and adapters to their most valuable commercial clients. What are the skills and qualities of a successful candidate in your organization? &amp;ldquo;Innovation, initiative and good communication.&amp;rdquo; In your opinion, what is the best way for UBC students to prepare for their interactions with you at the TCF? Know about the company and come prepared with specific questions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fortinet Technologies</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/fortinet-technologies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/fortinet-technologies/</guid>
      <description>Overview &amp;ldquo;Fortinet (NASDAQ: FTNT) is a worldwide provider of network security appliances and a market leader in Network Security (FW/NGFW/UTM). Our products and subscription services provide broad, integrated and high-performance protection against dynamic security threats while simplifying the IT security infrastructure. Our customers include enterprises, service providers and government entities worldwide, including the majority of the 2009 Fortune Global 100. Fortinet&amp;rsquo;s flagship FortiGate product delivers ASIC-accelerated performance and integrates multiple layers of security designed to help protect against application and network threats.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Galvanize</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/galvanize/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/galvanize/</guid>
      <description>Overview &amp;ldquo;Galvanize builds security, risk management, compliance, and audit software to drive change in some of the world&amp;rsquo;s largest organizations. We unite and strengthen individuals and entire companies through the integrated HighBond software platform.&amp;rdquo; What are the skills and qualities of a successful candidate in your organization? &amp;ldquo;As a new grad or a coop, it&amp;rsquo;s important for you to show a willingness and a passion to learn new things, and take on tasks that you are not sure how to accomplish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GeoGuard</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/geoguard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/geoguard/</guid>
      <description>Overview &amp;ldquo;A clear market-leader in Cyber-Security, GeoGuard specializes in fighting and detecting location fraud protecting regulated the industries as well as the global Film, TV &amp;amp; Sports world.
Working with some of the best known brands on the planet, GeoGuard delivers mission-critical solutions on a platform agnostic basis, across 200 million unique devices worldwide.&amp;rdquo; What are the skills and qualities of a successful candidate in your organization? &amp;ldquo;For someone to succeed in our organization is someone who truly embodies our values of build it better, bigger, right.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Global Relay Communications Inc.</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/global-relay-communications-inc./</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/global-relay-communications-inc./</guid>
      <description>Overview &amp;ldquo;Every day, your employees use communication platforms like email to talk to colleagues, customers, and counterparties. These platforms distribute critical information and keep your organization running efficiently. But they also produce a flood of data that can strain the resources of your IT and business teams.
We help organizations manage and control their communications data. Whether you want to meet regulatory requirements, streamline your eDiscovery process, or improve employee productivity, we can help you achieve your goals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ICBC</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/icbc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/icbc/</guid>
      <description>Overview &amp;ldquo;We&amp;rsquo;re committed to creating a workplace where employees know they are valued. Employee experience is a priority for us. Our core values are at the heart of who we are and what we do and our employee commitments guide us in promoting growth, well-being and a culture of caring-for our customers, our community and each other.&amp;rdquo; What are the skills and qualities of a successful candidate in your organization? &amp;ldquo;�Ability to work cooperatively within a team environment</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Infoblox Canada Ltd</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/infoblox-canada-ltd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/infoblox-canada-ltd/</guid>
      <description>Overview &amp;ldquo;Your organization depends on your network. And your network depends on DNS and related core network services to run reliably and securely.
Infoblox delivers Secure Cloud-Managed Network Services, bringing next-level security, reliability, and automation to cloud and hybrid systems; managed through a single pane of glass. We&amp;rsquo;re the market leader with over 50% of the worldwide DDI market share and over 8,000 customers (Including 93 of the Fortune 100, 350+ of the Fortune 500 and 58%+ of Fortune 1000); running the world&amp;rsquo;s most sophisticated networks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>InputHealth Systems Inc</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/inputhealth-systems-inc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/inputhealth-systems-inc/</guid>
      <description>Overview &amp;ldquo;At InputHealth, we build tools that make value-based healthcare possible through the ubiquity of mobile devices and cloud-based technology. We are committed to establishing an eHealth ecosystem that puts patients and healthcare providers at the centre of their own care. Rather than conforming to the electronic health record model currently being used in health care settings, we have created a Collaborative Health Record that allows for sharing of chart information with patients, tracking patient-reported outcome measures, video-conferencing, and empowering patients with tools such as health notifications and electronic appointment booking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JOMAR Softcorp Services Inc</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/jomar-softcorp-services-inc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/jomar-softcorp-services-inc/</guid>
      <description>Overview &amp;ldquo;JOMAR integrates &amp;lsquo;Next Generation IT&amp;rsquo; with the software development of our ERP Suite for Vertical Industry Sectors, Smart Grid Utility Systems, and insurance Applications based on a common architecture for implementation on multi-platform servers and deployment to the private Cloud on JOMAR Hosting Services in PEER1 locations.&amp;rdquo; What are the skills and qualities of a successful candidate in your organization? Good communication skills. Ability to communicate with customers. Works well with a team and independent environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kabam Games, Inc.</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/kabam-games/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/kabam-games/</guid>
      <description>Overview &amp;ldquo;We&amp;rsquo;re a gaming company that strives for creativity, focuses on collaboration and, most importantly, loves to have fun! Partnering with iconic entertainment brands like Disney, Hasbro and Universal, we create immersive and engaging mobile games for the world to enjoy.
Kabam&amp;rsquo;s games have generated hundreds of millions of downloads including Fast &amp;amp; Furious 6: The Game, Fast &amp;amp; Furious: Legacy, Marvel Contest of Champions, Transformers: Forged to Fight, Shop Titans and Mini Guns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ledcor</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/ledcor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/ledcor/</guid>
      <description>Overview &amp;ldquo;The Ledcor Group of Companies is one of North America&amp;rsquo;s most diversified construction companies, serving the civil &amp;amp; infrastructure, oil &amp;amp; gas, pipeline, building, mining, power, and telecommunications sectors. Ledcor also owns operations in property investment, forestry, aviation, and marine transportation services. Ledcor employs over 7000 people across 20 offices. Ledcor is a privately-held, employee-owned company with over 800 employee shareholders. Since 1947 the company has been growing with its clients and partners: Forward.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microchip</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/microchip/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/microchip/</guid>
      <description>Overview &amp;ldquo;Leading provider of high-speed broadband communications and storage semiconductors and MIPS-based processors for Enterprise, Access, Metro Optical Transport, and Storage Area Networking.&amp;rdquo; What are the skills and qualities of a successful candidate in your organization? &amp;ldquo;Good communication skills, fast learner, strong drive to learn new things, team player&amp;rdquo; In your opinion, what is the best way for UBC students to prepare for their interactions with you at the TCF? &amp;ldquo;Bring your resume; be ready to speak with managers and engineers at our booth, ask about our products and technology, and tell us your interest and aspirations!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Motion Metrics International Corp</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/motion-metrics-international-corp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/motion-metrics-international-corp/</guid>
      <description>Overview &amp;ldquo;At Motion Metrics our teams brings the experience of an established company and the enthusiasm of a fast-moving start-up venture. Since 2004, our engineers have leveraged the latest techniques in machine learning, robotics, and remote sensing to deliver innovative monitoring solutions to mines around the world. Today, applied AI defines us. We&amp;rsquo;re a tight-knit team of visionaries and disruptors who drive industry change through the application of leading-edge technologies.With two modern offices (UBC and Downtown) we are always looking for top talent to join our expert team of engineers and skilled professionals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Munvo Solutions</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/munvo-solutions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/munvo-solutions/</guid>
      <description>Overview &amp;ldquo;We are a leading consulting firm assisting global companies with marketing software solutions. On top of our professional software implementation services for Adobe, SAS, and Unica marketing solutions, we also develop custom products and connectors tailored to our clients&amp;rsquo; needs. Munvo&amp;rsquo;s team of over 90 employees can be found at any of our centralized offices in Calgary, Montreal, and Toronto.&amp;rdquo; What are the skills and qualities of a successful candidate in your organization?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NetApp</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/netapp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/netapp/</guid>
      <description>Overview &amp;ldquo;NetApp creates innovative storage and data management solutions that deliver outstanding cost efficiency and accelerate business breakthroughs. Customers around the world choose us for our &amp;ldquo;&amp;ldquo;go beyond&amp;rdquo;&amp;rdquo; approach and broad portfolio of products and services. Our solutions can help you deploy new capabilities with confidence and get to revenue faster than ever before.
With NetApp, customers store and manage the data that enable them to do some amazing things. � Within three days of the Japanese earthquake and tsunami, SOFTBANK Group delivered cloud services to a nation, enabling people to get online and stay productive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Creation Consulting</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/new-creation-consulting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/new-creation-consulting/</guid>
      <description>Overview &amp;ldquo;New Creation Consulting and NCOL Internet serve a diverse client base across North America. We are in our 22nd incorporated year, with a history of delivering spectacular web-based solutions for our clients.&amp;rdquo; What are the skills and qualities of a successful candidate in your organization? &amp;ldquo;The successful candidate: - will have superior people skills, including verbal and written communication; - understands the importance of timely and accurate communication and client service; - understands and uses project management principles, with strong attention to detail; - is a team player who takes responsibility in a supportive team setting; and - will thrive in a fast-paced, self-directed environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Orbis</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/orbis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/orbis/</guid>
      <description>Overview &amp;ldquo;Orbis is a global, privately owned investment firm, managing in excess of US$30 billion of assets with offices across 5 continents and over 400 professionals. We have been creating long-term value for our clients since 1990. Our investment philosophy is fundamental, long-term and contrarian and we are uniquely structured to encourage bold but considered decisions, even in times of stress. As a firm, our business model requires us to deliver meaningful outperformance to our clients.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PDFTron Systems, Inc.</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/pdftron/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/pdftron/</guid>
      <description>Overview &amp;ldquo;PDFTron Systems Inc. is changing the way the world works with documents. PDFTron is an industry-leading provider of document processing technology that powers everything from traditional desktop software (like AutoCAD), to web apps (like DocuSign), and mobile apps (like Xodo).
We are a fast growing company and have just secured a $95M strategic growth investment.
We foster an atmosphere of opportunity, growth, and success for every single individual amidst an exciting, challenging, and entrepreneurial culture where career progression is based on merit, not tenure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ping Identity</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/ping-identity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/ping-identity/</guid>
      <description>Overview &amp;ldquo;At Ping Identity, we&amp;rsquo;re changing the way people think about enterprise security technology. With our innovative Identity Defined Security platform, we&amp;rsquo;re helping to build a borderless world where people have total freedom to work wherever and however they want. Without friction. Without fear.
We&amp;rsquo;re headquartered in Denver, Colorado, and we have offices and employees around the globe. And we serve the largest, most demanding enterprises worldwide, including over half of the Fortune 100.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Qumulo</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/qumulo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/qumulo/</guid>
      <description>Overview &amp;ldquo;At Qumulo we&amp;rsquo;ve built a truly unique distributed file system from scratch. It wasn&amp;rsquo;t easy and it&amp;rsquo;s far from a finished product. Joining Qumulo&amp;rsquo;s team of elite engineers means working on an innovative product at its infancy and watching your work take effect. It&amp;rsquo;s an opportunity to work directly with customers and increase the value of our product by solving their most challenging problems.
We hire smart, adaptive engineers with diverse backgrounds and a knack for taking challenges head on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RAPTOR INTEGRATION INC</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/raptor-integration-inc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/raptor-integration-inc/</guid>
      <description>Overview &amp;ldquo;Raptor Integration Inc. is a modern and innovative company focused on industrial process automation, with roots in the forest industry. Our sophisticated measurement tools employ an array of sensor technologies: vision, X-ray, and laser. Our control systems complete the process by automating the machinery and reporting results back to enterprise information system. Raptor solutions are designed for immediate needs and provide flexibility for future adaptations.&amp;rdquo; What are the skills and qualities of a successful candidate in your organization?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>realtor.com</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/realtor.com/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/realtor.com/</guid>
      <description>Overview &amp;ldquo;realtor.com� is the trusted resource for home buyers, sellers and dreamers. We give consumers the information they need to move confidently throughout their home journey while keeping professionals at the heart of the transaction. It&amp;rsquo;s our mission to make all things home simple, efficient and enjoyable.
realtor.com� was founded in 1995, and is headquartered in the heart of Silicon Valley, Santa Clara, California and also has an office in Richmond, BC which houses 250+ employees.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RedMane Technology</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/redmane-technology/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/redmane-technology/</guid>
      <description>Overview &amp;ldquo;RedMane provides software solutions and systems integration services that address complex, real-world challenges. More than anything else, we&amp;rsquo;re a problem-solving company. Technology is just our tool.&amp;rdquo; What are the skills and qualities of a successful candidate in your organization? &amp;ldquo;Excellent Verbal and Written communication, team player, good understanding of development process. Indigenous studies would be an added bonus.&amp;rdquo; In your opinion, what is the best way for UBC students to prepare for their interactions with you at the TCF?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reliable Controls</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/reliable-controls/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/reliable-controls/</guid>
      <description>Overview &amp;ldquo;Reliable Controls Corporation specializes in the design and manufacture of Internet-connected, building automation controls. Our innovative products automate building environments, decreasing their impact on our planet. As a privately-owned, Canadian corporation since 1986, we are dedicated to providing simple, flexible, and sustainable systems, economically targeted to meet the triple bottom line of people, planet, and profit. We are proud to have design, development, assembly, service, and repairs housed in Victoria, Canada.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rogers Communications</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/rogers-communications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/rogers-communications/</guid>
      <description>Overview &amp;ldquo;Rogers is a leading diversified Canadian communications and media company. We are Canada&amp;rsquo;s largest provider of wireless communications services and one of Canada&amp;rsquo;s leading providers of cable television, high-speed Internet, information technology, and telephony services to consumers and businesses. Through Rogers Media, we are engaged in radio and television broadcasting, sports, televised and online shopping, and digital media.&amp;rdquo; What are the skills and qualities of a successful candidate in your organization?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Safe Software Inc.</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/safe-software-inc./</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/safe-software-inc./</guid>
      <description>Overview &amp;ldquo;Safe Software Inc. is the maker of FME� and the global leader in spatial data transformation technology that helps GIS professionals and organizations master their data interoperability challenges.
FME is used by thousands of customers in more than 116 countries in a variety of industries. Ranging from small businesses to top international organizations, our customers use FME to unleash the power of their spatial data so people can use it where, when, and how they want to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SambaNova Systems</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/sambanova-systems/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/sambanova-systems/</guid>
      <description>Overview &amp;ldquo;SambaNova Systems is a rapidly growing startup that is powering the next generation of Machine Learning and AI. Using technology born at Stanford, we are building a software stack and specialized processor that allows deep learning applications to run orders of magnitudes faster than on traditional hardware. We are re-imagining what these applications are capable of by re-inventing the platforms they run on. Our team has a wealth of hardware experience and a track record of building and shipping chips.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SAP</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/sap/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/sap/</guid>
      <description>Overview &amp;ldquo;As the Experience Company powered by the Intelligent Enterprise, SAP is the market leader in enterprise application software, helping companies of all sizes and in all industries run at their best. Our machine learning, Internet of Things (IoT), and advanced analytics technologies help turn customers&amp;rsquo; businesses into intelligent enterprises. We simplify technology for companies so they can consume our software the way they want - without disruption. Our end-to-end suite of applications and services enables more than 437,000 business and public customers to operate profitably, adapt continuously, and make a difference.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skybox Labs</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/skybox-labs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/skybox-labs/</guid>
      <description>Overview &amp;ldquo;SkyBox Labs is a full-service game development studio based in Vancouver, BC, Canada. Founded in 2011, we&amp;rsquo;ve developed titles alongside some of the world&amp;rsquo;s top publishers including Xbox Game Studios, GungHo, and Electronic Arts. Our current projects include working as a co-developer on Halo Infinite, projects in the Minecraft Universe, and original cinematic platformer, Stela.&amp;rdquo; What are the skills and qualities of a successful candidate in your organization? &amp;ldquo;- proficiency in C++ - proficiency in Unity game engine - strong communication skills - team work skills - interest in growing, learning, and supporting others with growth and learning - self-motivated - passion for game development!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skycope Technologies Inc</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/skycope-technologies-inc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/skycope-technologies-inc/</guid>
      <description>Overview &amp;ldquo;Founded in 2016, Skycope Technologies Inc. is a high tech security company based in Burnaby, Canada.
Applying the latest RF spectrum sensing and manipulation technologies, we provide the most advanced anti-drone solutions. Our technology can safely and effectively detect, identify, and neutralize rogue drones to prevent them from posing security threats in unauthorized areas.
Our team is a collection of diverse, talented and hard-working professionals who enjoy attacking challenging and significant problems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sophos</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/sophos/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/sophos/</guid>
      <description>Overview &amp;ldquo;Sophos - Cybersecurity Evolved
Sophos evolves to meet every new challenge, protecting more than 400,000 organizations of all sizes in more than 150 countries from today&amp;rsquo;s most advanced cyberthreats. Powered by SophosLabs, our cloud-native and AI-enhanced solutions are able to adapt and evolve to secure endpoints and networks against never-before-seen cybercriminal tactics and techniques. Managed through our award-winning, cloud-based platform, Sophos Central, our best-of-breed products work together through our unique Synchronized Security system to share threat intelligence and respond to evolving threats.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Splunk</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/splunk/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/splunk/</guid>
      <description>Overview &amp;ldquo;Join us as we pursue our disruptive new vision to make machine data accessible, usable and valuable to everyone. We are a company filled with people who are passionate about our product and seek to deliver the best experience for our customers. At Splunk, we&amp;rsquo;re committed to our work, customers, having fun and most importantly to each other&amp;rsquo;s success. Learn more about Splunk careers and how you can become a part of our journey!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SSI</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/ssi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/ssi/</guid>
      <description>Overview &amp;ldquo;SSI develops Autodesk based solutions for the shipbuilding and offshore industry including: ShipConstructor software, an AutoCAD based CAD/CAM product line; and EnterprisePlatform, a tool for sharing product data model information. Expert consultation is also available to ensure real time engineering data passes effortlessly between applications such as MRP, ERP or PLM tools. Shipbuilders, naval architects and marine engineers trust SSI on projects such as yachts, oil rigs, tankers, ferries, warships and workboats.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tableau</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/tableau/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/tableau/</guid>
      <description>Overview &amp;ldquo;A mission that matters
We help people see and understand their data. Eight words that drive everything we do. And they&amp;rsquo;ve never been more important.
In 2020 the world will generate 50 times the amount of data as in 2011 and 75 times the number of information sources (IDC, 2011). Within these data are huge opportunities for human advancement. But to turn opportunities into reality, people need the power of data at their fingertips.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teck Resources Ltd.</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/teck-resources-ltd./</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/teck-resources-ltd./</guid>
      <description>Overview &amp;ldquo;Teck is a diversified resource company committed to responsible mining and mineral development with business units focused on copper, zinc, steelmaking coal and energy. We have received several awards and recognitions that are worth noting. Teck was selected as one of Canada&amp;rsquo;s Top 100 Employers in both 2018 and 2019, Teck was recognized as one of the Global 100 Most Sustainable Corporations in 2019 and in 2018 and Teck was also ranked on the Corporate Knights Best 50 for the 12th straight year based on our dedication to environmental sustainability, and social responsibility.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TELUS GTLP</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/telus-gtlp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/telus-gtlp/</guid>
      <description>Overview &amp;ldquo;TELUS&amp;rsquo; Graduate Technology Leadership Program (GTLP), formerly the GELP, is a one-of-a-kind technical development program with a focus on technology and innovation. Complete 3 nine-month rotations across five possible technology streams. Get exposed to a breadth of functions through a series of rotations and projects while delivering on the technology needs of our customers.&amp;rdquo; What are the skills and qualities of a successful candidate in your organization? &amp;ldquo;Excellent verbal and written communication skills, team player, strong understanding of computer science fundamentals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teradici Corporation</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/teradici-corporation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/teradici-corporation/</guid>
      <description>Overview &amp;ldquo;Teradici is the technology leader for creating secure workspaces. Our unique ingredient approach allows our partners to offer a broad range of solutions. The world&amp;rsquo;s largest cloud computing companies rely on our PCoIP technology to fulfill the promise of the cloud - an outstanding user experience, securely delivered to any device, anywhere.&amp;rdquo; What are the skills and qualities of a successful candidate in your organization? &amp;ldquo;New graduates join one of our scrum teams where they can immediately become an active contributor to our software code base for our products.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TTT Studios</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/ttt-studios/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/ttt-studios/</guid>
      <description>Overview &amp;ldquo;TTT is an award winning Digital Innovation Studio, building custom software for more than 150 clients around the world. We work with industry leaders and challengers who have ambitious goals and see the value in re-shaping their industries through technology. With experience across 20+ different industries, our technical capabilities include mobile development, AR &amp;amp; VR, IoT, AI, cloud computing, and enterprise solutions.
When we&amp;rsquo;re not building software, we enjoy hosting and supporting community events such as meetups, workshops and hackathons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubisoft Montreal</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/ubisoft-montreal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/ubisoft-montreal/</guid>
      <description>Overview &amp;ldquo;At Ubisoft Montreal, a preeminent developer of video games located in Montreal&amp;rsquo;s dynamic Mile-End neighbourhood since 1997, we offer a work environment unique in the industry for allowing you to build and cultivate games that are part of critically acclaimed, iconic AAA franchises of international repute.
When you join Ubi Montreal, you enter a community of passionate, extraordinary developers connected by their need to innovate, to be creative and to work with the latest technology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visier Inc.</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/visier-inc./</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/visier-inc./</guid>
      <description>Overview &amp;ldquo;A leading innovator in Applied Big Data cloud technology, Visier provides Workforce Intelligence solutions that are enabling a rapidly growing number of the world&amp;rsquo;s best brands to maximize their business outcomes through their people.
Visier&amp;rsquo;s solutions let organizations understand and plan - with precision - how to best and most cost-effectively recruit, retain, and develop their workforce. With Visier, senior leaders, HR, and people managers alike can answer key workforce questions, align on goals and strategies, and act on decisions and plans to drive improved business outcomes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vizzion</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/vizzion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/vizzion/</guid>
      <description>Overview &amp;ldquo;Vizzion provides data and services to brand names such as Microsoft, Mercedes-Benz and MapQuest. Our traffic camera software solutions are used by millions of users every week, saving them time, money and frustration, while also helping the environment by reducing vehicle emissions.
As a company we value integrity, quality over quantity, automation, and continuous improvement. We make products and services that are novel, intuitive, scalable, high-performance, reliable, and economical, and back them up with outstanding customer service.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>