<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>UBC Technical Career Fair</title>
    <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/premiums/</link>
    <description>Recent content on UBC Technical Career Fair</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ubctcf.com/companies/premiums/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Benevity Inc.</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/premiums/benevity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/premiums/benevity/</guid>
      <description>Better Work and a Better World: at Benevity that’s what we’re all about. We’re a software company in the business of doing good, building better ways for companies to connect with their customers and employees around causes (we make “doing well by doing good” more than just a tagline!). We’re growing fast and looking for more great people to join us.
We’re not Bono, just a passionate crew of workhorses out to change the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Motion Metrics International</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/premiums/motion-metrics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/premiums/motion-metrics/</guid>
      <description>With over fifteen years of experience, Motion Metrics applies the latest in artificial intelligence and deep learning techniques to solve tough safety and efficiency related challenges in mines, quarries, and industrial sites around the world. As a growing company, we are always searching for new talent with a passion for developing cutting-edge technology. Motion Metrics is looking for engineers, developers, and computer scientists from all disciplines and backgrounds to join our diverse team at our headquarters in Vancouver, BC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Orbis</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/premiums/orbis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/premiums/orbis/</guid>
      <description>Orbis is a privately-held global investment management firm that invests over $25 billion in capital. The firm manages several performance-driven equity funds in both long-only and absolute return strategies using a long-term, fundamental, contrarian investment approach. Orbis employs approximately 400 people in eight countries, who represent more than 35 nationalities, speak more than 15 languages and come from a wide range of educational and professional backgrounds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PDFTron Systems Inc.</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/premiums/pdftron/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/premiums/pdftron/</guid>
      <description>PDFTron Systems Inc. is a premier provider of standards-based document technologies related to PDF, XPS, SVG, ePub, MS Office, HTML, and other graphic file formats. PDFTron&amp;rsquo;s cross-platform, high-performance developer components power well-known commercial products, complex enterprise-wide document management and publishing workflows, as well as high-traffic web-based applications, changing how we use documents one application at a time in virtually all industry areas.
PDFTron fosters an atmosphere of opportunity, growth, and success for every single individual amidst an exciting, challenging and entrepreneurial culture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tableau</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/premiums/tableau/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/premiums/tableau/</guid>
      <description>Tableau Software is an American computer software company headquartered in Seattle, Washington. It produces a family of interactive data visualization products focused on business intelligence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TTT Studios</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/premiums/ttt-studios/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/premiums/ttt-studios/</guid>
      <description>TTT Studio is a world-class software development Company working for a global client list in multiple industries. Over the past 9 years, we have built multiple applications and patented a portfolio of technologies. This experience puts us in the best position to cater larger accounts and launch our own products.
We are a family. We have fun. Design means everything to us and we have the technical chops to deliver what lesser programmers might describe as spooky magic.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>