<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>UBC Technical Career Fair 2019</title>
    <link>https://ubctcf.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on UBC Technical Career Fair 2019</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2016 19:46:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ubctcf.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2016 19:46:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/privacy/</guid>
      <description>Privacy Policy Data Collected All activities performed on the TCF webapp will be logged anonymously through Google Analytics. No personally identifiable information is ever recorded through this method.
Additionally, all hits to company pages will be logged internally, and will be associated with an IP address. If logged in, we will additionally record this hit with your user account associated with it. This information is used solely for the purposes of improving the system and event, and is not shared with any third parties.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/map/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/map/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Thinking Ape</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/a-thinking-ape/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/a-thinking-ape/</guid>
      <description>A Thinking Ape is a small yet driven team that is dedicated to building strong mobile communities.
With our collaborative approach to product design, we ensure the best ideas get the space they need to grow.
Our team seeks out intuitive solutions to complex problems, and maintains strong ties to our hacker culture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Absolute Software</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/absolute/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/absolute/</guid>
      <description>Absolute provides persistent endpoint security and data risk management solutions for computers, tablets, and smartphones. Our customers rely on us to provide them with a unique and trusted layer of security so they can manage mobility while remaining firmly in control. Our Persistence technology is embedded into the core of most devices at the factory. Once activated, it provides you with comprehensive visibility into all of your devices enabling you to confidently manage mobility, investigate potential threats, and take action if a security incident occurs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazon</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/amazon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/amazon/</guid>
      <description>At Amazon, our evolution has been driven by the spirit of innovation that is part of our DNA. As a new college graduate or intern, you can have multiple opportunities to innovate and solve real-world, complex technical and business problems as you join us on our journey. We strive to hire the brightest minds from universities around the globe, and have various career opportunities available for undergraduates and advanced degree students with diverse academic backgrounds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aquatic Informatics</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/aquatic-infomatics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/aquatic-infomatics/</guid>
      <description>Aquatic Informatics™ provides leading software solutions that address critical water data management and analysis challenges for the rapidly growing environmental monitoring industry. Aquatic Informatics is the trusted provider of hydrologic management solutions to hundreds of federal, state/provincial and local government departments, hydropower operators, mining companies, academic groups, and consulting organizations around the world, who collect, manage, and process large volumes of water quality or quantity data.
Aquatic Informatics has earned a global reputation for innovation in environmental data management.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arista Networks</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/arista-networks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/arista-networks/</guid>
      <description>Arista Networks was founded to deliver cloud networking solutions for large data center and computing environments. Arista offers a broad portfolio of Gigabit Ethernet solutions including 1,10 and 40 GbE switches that redefine network architectures, bring extensibility to networking and dramatically change the price/performance of data center networks. At the core of Arista&amp;rsquo;s platform is EOS (Extensible Operating System), the world&amp;rsquo;s most advanced network operating system, designed to build software defined cloud networks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Avigilon</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/avigilon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/avigilon/</guid>
      <description>Pronunciation: a-vigil-on Definition: To be perpetually alert and watchful
Avigilon designs, develops, and manufactures video analytics, network video management software and hardware, surveillance cameras, and access control solutions. Avigilon&amp;rsquo;s solutions have been installed at thousands of customer sites, including school campuses, transportation systems, healthcare centers, public venues, critical infrastructure, prisons, factories, casinos, airports, financial institutions, government facilities, and retailer</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Benevity Inc.</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/benevity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/benevity/</guid>
      <description>Better Work and a Better World: at Benevity that’s what we’re all about. We’re a software company in the business of doing good, building better ways for companies to connect with their customers and employees around causes (we make “doing well by doing good” more than just a tagline!). We’re growing fast and looking for more great people to join us.
We’re not Bono, just a passionate crew of workhorses out to change the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Broadridge Financial Solutions, Inc</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/broadridge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/broadridge/</guid>
      <description>Broadridge is the leading provider of investor communications, technology-driven solutions, and data and analytics for wealth management, asset management, capital markets firms, and corporations. We help clients drive operational excellence to manage risk, accelerate growth, and deliver real business value. Broadridge&amp;rsquo;s technology-driven solutions power the entire investment lifecycle, enabling clients to successfully manage the complexity of today’s capital markets and communicate with customers and investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CPP Investment Board</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/cpp-investment-board/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/cpp-investment-board/</guid>
      <description>We have a profound responsibility: to invest the assets belonging to 20 million Canadians to help ensure the sustainability of the Canada Pension Plan.
To meet this responsibility, CPPIB was created with a singular investment objective: to maximize returns without undue risk of loss. In doing so we are explicitly required to act in the best interests of contributors and beneficiaries and take into account the factors that affect the financial obligations of the CPP.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Canfor</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/canfor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/canfor/</guid>
      <description>Canfor is one of the world’s largest producers of sustainable lumber, pulp and paper and a North American leader in green energy production. As we seek to raise the bar in how we do business, we constantly invest in cutting-edge technology and make innovation a priority.
We’re also committed to sustainable forest management, which includes planting over 75 million trees annually and having independently certified forest management systems.
The foundation of our company is based on a set of values and guiding principles that reflects who we are as a company and what we believe in as a group of individuals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Capital One</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/capital-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/capital-one/</guid>
      <description>We are defining the next generation of banking in Canada, challenging the brick and mortar status quo. We’re looking for well-rounded and passionate students to join our high performing culture focused on customer-centric design and data driven problem solving.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clio</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/clio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/clio/</guid>
      <description>Clio is the most comprehensive cloud-based practice management platform for the legal industry. With the help of the cloud, Clio eases the process of time tracking, billing, administration, and collaboration for law firms of all sizes. Based in Vancouver, B.C. and launched in 2008, Clio is used by legal professionals in over 50 countries. Clio has raised $27 million from investors including Bessemer Venture Partners. Learn more at www.clio.com.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ComingSoon</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/comingsoon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/comingsoon/</guid>
      <description> Coming Soon! </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Communications Security Establishment</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/cse/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/cse/</guid>
      <description>The Communications Security Establishment is one of Canada’s key security and intelligence organizations. For 70 years CSE has been committed to the safety and security of Canada and Canadians. We focus on collecting foreign signals intelligence to protect Canada against threats, and on helping protect the computer networks and information of greatest importance to Canada. We also provide technical assistance to federal law enforcement and security organizations Our work helps to ensure our nation’s security and stability; protecting against foreign-based terrorism and espionage, cyber-attacks, and other serious threats.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Copperleaf Technologies</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/copperleaf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/copperleaf/</guid>
      <description>Building a better world one decision at a time. Copperleaf provides Decision Analytics to companies facing the challenges of managing critical infrastructure. Our enterprise software solutions leverage operational and financial data to help our clients make investment decisions that deliver the highest value to their stakeholders. Copperleaf’s dynamic risk and value framework, predictive analytics, state-of-the-art optimization, and interactive visualizations empower businesses to make complex investment decisions with confidence. In 2016, Canadian Business Magazine named Copperleaf as one of the top 20 fastest-growing software companies in Canada.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>D2L Corporation</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/d2l-corporation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/d2l-corporation/</guid>
      <description>D2L was founded in 1999 by John Baker. At the time, his engineering class was being challenged to look at the world in new ways by coming up with questions that no one had asked before.
John realized that despite all the change technology was driving in the world, his University campus seemed almost untouched by that momentum. The question he wanted to ask was clear: how could we use technology to dramatically transform learning?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deloitte</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/deloitte/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/deloitte/</guid>
      <description>At Deloitte, every day your work will make an impact that matters. And you’ll thrive in a dynamic culture of high performance, inclusion, flexibility, and build lifelong relationships within a powerful global network.
Here, we empower our people to be the very best they can be so they can make a difference, not only for clients, colleagues, and communities, but also for their own careers and aspirations. At Deloitte, we invest in our people and help them leverage their strengths.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Delta Controls</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/delta-controls/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/delta-controls/</guid>
      <description>Delta is often described as a family. We call our Distributors ‘Partners’ because we recognize that their success is closely linked to ours. Our staff are even closer and we see the same longevity and stability in our workforce as we do in our Partner channel.
Most of us are geeks at heart and it is great fun to work with people as excited about electrical engineering and software development as we are – smart people who want to push technology forward.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Double Negative</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/double-negative/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/double-negative/</guid>
      <description>We are Double Negative (DNEG), one of the world’s leading visual effects and animation companies for feature film and television, with studios in London, Vancouver, Mumbai, Los Angeles, Chennai and Montréal.
Founded with a team of just 30 in London in 1998, we now employ over 2,500 people across our global offices. Our creative drive and close collaborative working relationship with filmmakers ensures that the projects that we work on, large and small, all receive the same high standards of creative and technical service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>East Side Games</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/east-side-games/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/east-side-games/</guid>
      <description>East Side Games is a proudly independent and profitable game studio creating humorous and addicting games for mobile and social platforms.
We have a collaborative, creative, and fun culture that is focused on building hit titles in a great work environment. Our talented, highly-motivated team believes in constantly improving; we are not afraid to take ownership and meet challenges head-on in order to reach our goals.
Purpose-built technology infrastructure powers our rapid, iterative prototyping, based directly on audience feedback.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FDM Group</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/fdm-group/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/fdm-group/</guid>
      <description>FDM Group is a global professional services provider with a focus on IT. With over 180 clients worldwide and over 3000 IT and business consultants, FDM brings people and technology together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finger Food Studios</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/finger-food-studios/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/finger-food-studios/</guid>
      <description>Finger Food is a world-class technology company that designs and develops immersive Mobile, MR/AR/VR, Internet of Things, Machine Learning, Cloud and Entertainment products. Our work transforms industries. We are passionate about embracing and innovating bleeding-edge technological opportunities and delivering products that achieve tangible ROI in real-world scenarios.
We work with iOS, Android, Microsoft HoloLens, Tango, Oculus, HTC Vive, and Unity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fortinet Technologies</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/fortinet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/fortinet/</guid>
      <description>Fortinet is a global leader in providing Cyber security solutions. We develop next generation firewall systems and high end Security Systems like Fortigate, FortiSandbox, FortiAnalyzer, Forticlient and many other products to enterprise security to our clients which also includes Fortune 100 companies. Our flagship enterprise firewall platform, FortiGate, is available in a wide range of sizes and form factors to fit any environment, and provides a broad array of next generation security and networking functions covering Network security, Data center security (physical and virtual), Cloud security, Secure (wired and wireless) access, Infrastructure (switching and routing) security, Content security, Endpoint security, Application Security.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Global Relay</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/global-relay/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/global-relay/</guid>
      <description>Global Relay is the leading provider of cloud-based electronic message archiving, supervision, and eDiscovery solutions for the global financial sector, delivering services to 20,000 customers in 90 countries, including 22 of the world’s top 25 banks. Global Relay Archive securely captures and preserves email, instant messaging, mobile messaging, Bloomberg, Thomson Reuters, Twitter, LinkedIn, Facebook and more — with Blackberry, iPhone, iPad, Android, Outlook and Web access.
Apply today – we have five floors of great open space offices with a fast-paced vibe, lots of amenities, a roof top deck &amp;amp; BBQ, and an in-house chef, all located in the heart of Gastown near Waterfront Station.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Groundswell Cloud Solutions</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/groundswell-cloud-solutions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/groundswell-cloud-solutions/</guid>
      <description>Salesforce Is In Our DNA
We drive businesses forward with a one-size-doesn&amp;rsquo;t-fit-all approach.
We Embrace Challenges
Founded by a former Salesforce.com veteran, we take our reputation for being master problem-solvers seriously. Over the years we have delivered some of the most challenging Salesforce implementation projects imaginable—making us the partner of choice for companies facing a complex challenge with no ‘out of the box’ solution.
Success Through Partnerships
Coming from humble origins, the team has grown significantly over the years, and continues to do so at a rapid rate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HERE Technologies</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/here-technologies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/here-technologies/</guid>
      <description>Mapping has always been about discovery. For centuries, two-dimensional maps guided us through the unknown to our destination. But we are no longer limited by the edges of our physical maps.
In 1985, we began with the simple goal to digitize mapping and pioneer in-car navigation systems. Over the next three decades, as NAVTEQ and Nokia, we’ve built a legacy in mapping technology.
Today, we&amp;rsquo;re creating living three-dimensional maps that grow upwards, breathing with layers of information and insights.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hootsuite</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/hootsuite/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/hootsuite/</guid>
      <description>A social media management platform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intel of Canada</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/intel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/intel/</guid>
      <description>The Non-Volatile Memory Solutions Group is a worldwide organization that delivers NAND flash memory products for use in Solid State Drives (SSDs), portable memory storage devices, digital camera memory cards, and other devices.
The Vancouver design center develops products for Intel&amp;rsquo;s solid-state drive group. This team is comprised of design engineers with expertise in the areas of ASIC, FPGA, firmware, hardware, and mechanical design.
The Vancouver office is located just south of downtown in the desirable, and centrally located, Fairview neighborhood.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Konrad</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/konrad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/konrad/</guid>
      <description>Konrad is a global digital agency and innovation firm that serves a world-class and diverse client base. We help our clients identify, plan for, and capitalize on digital opportunity wherever it is found. With a decade of experience delivering success and a global team of 250+ practitioners, we are uniquely positioned to deliver on this mandate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsemi</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/microsemi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/microsemi/</guid>
      <description>Leading provider of high-speed broadband communications and storage semiconductors and MIPS-based processors for Enterprise, Access, Metro Optical Transport, and Storage Area Networking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/microsoft/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/microsoft/</guid>
      <description>We run our business in much the same way. Our employees come as they are and do what they love. Imagine the opportunities you’ll have in a company with 100,000 employees in more than 100 countries, working on hundreds of products—spanning games, phones, developer tools, business solutions and operating systems. We work hard, but we value work/life balance, and each of us defines what that means to us. So why not explore what we do, where we do it, and what life is really like at Microsoft.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Motion Metrics International</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/motion-metrics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/motion-metrics/</guid>
      <description>With over fifteen years of experience, Motion Metrics applies the latest in artificial intelligence and deep learning techniques to solve tough safety and efficiency related challenges in mines, quarries, and industrial sites around the world. As a growing company, we are always searching for new talent with a passion for developing cutting-edge technology. Motion Metrics is looking for engineers, developers, and computer scientists from all disciplines and backgrounds to join our diverse team at our headquarters in Vancouver, BC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NCOL Internet</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/ncol-internet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/ncol-internet/</guid>
      <description>NCOL Internet is about people – communicating effectively – with customers and clients, with teammates and peers, and with their organization – via the Internet.
The NCOL Internet team consists of business process consultants, web strategists, technical architects, trainers, designers and project managers with major clients in multiple markets, NCOL Internet helps to define opportunities and leverage Internet technologies to meet your unique business needs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Need Help?</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/help/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/help/</guid>
      <description>Need Help? If you need any assistance during the event, you have several options
Find a Volunteer Volunteers will be walking around the venue, and they&amp;rsquo;re all sporting an awesome TCF badge so they&amp;rsquo;re easy to spot.
Visit the Info Booth This booth is located at the front of the venue, and you probably passed it on the way in. Helpful volunteers will always be stationed here.
Contact Us Directly If you can&amp;rsquo;t find anyone and need help right away, just contact the CSSS VP External.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NetApp</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/netapp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/netapp/</guid>
      <description>Leading organizations worldwide count on NetApp for software, systems and services to manage and store their data. Customers value our teamwork, expertise and passion for helping them succeed now and into the future.
Creating a model company is at the heart of everything we do. This means delivering value to each community we serve: customers, shareholders, employees, partners, and neighbors.
We are committed to living our core values: • Trust and Integrity • Leadership • Simplicity • Adaptability • Teamwork • Go Beyond • Get Things Done The strength of our culture means that we attract the industry’s best to work for our customers’ success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Hippo Health</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/new-hippo-health/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/new-hippo-health/</guid>
      <description>Are you motivated to work on products that have a meaningful impact? At New Hippo Health, our mission is to build software products to fundamentally improve the Canadian healthcare system for patients, their family and friends, specialists, and clinical care teams. We are a Vancouver-based startup founded by the CEOs of three notable companies: Crystal Decisions, Pulse Energy, and Eupraxia Pharmaceuticals. Our distributed team is cross-functional and features clinical, business, technical, creative, and artistic talent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Orbis</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/orbis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/orbis/</guid>
      <description>Orbis is a privately-held global investment management firm that invests over $25 billion in capital. The firm manages several performance-driven equity funds in both long-only and absolute return strategies using a long-term, fundamental, contrarian investment approach. Orbis employs approximately 400 people in eight countries, who represent more than 35 nationalities, speak more than 15 languages and come from a wide range of educational and professional backgrounds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PNI Digital Media</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/pni/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/pni/</guid>
      <description>We develop the next-generation technologies for the world&amp;rsquo;s largest retailers for which we&amp;rsquo;ve become world renown. In addition to revolutionizing the users&amp;rsquo; online experience, we use our world-class programming skills to innovate the systems for the production and fulfillment of their orders. What is more impressive is the scale and reach of our solutions servicing millions of customers and transactions all around the globe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ping Identity</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/ping-identity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/ping-identity/</guid>
      <description>Our mission is to simplify how enterprises provide secure and seamless digital experiences. For the world’s largest organizations, we help prevent security breaches, increase employee and partner productivity and provide personalized customer experiences. Enterprises choose Ping for our identity expertise, open standards leadership, partnership with companies like Microsoft, Amazon and Google, and collaboration with customers like Boeing, Cisco, Disney, GE, Kraft Foods, Walgreens and over half of the Fortune 100.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Realtor.com</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/realtor-com/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/realtor-com/</guid>
      <description>Realtor.com®, operated by Move, Inc., is the fastest growing online real estate destination for homebuyers, sellers and renters. Today, with over 3 million listings from nearly 800 multiple listing services (MLS), we have the most homes for sale nationwide than any competing real estate marketplaces.
At realtor.com®, we’re on a mission to give people everywhere the power to discover their next dream home, from anywhere. We’re building world-class real estate solutions that empower realtors with the tools, knowledge and confidence they need to connect people with their perfect home to grow their business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RedMane Technology Canada</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/redmane/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/redmane/</guid>
      <description>RedMane Technology is a software development company. We have been in business for 16 years and have recently opened up our Canada Delivery Practice in Burnaby, British Columbia.
We do the hard stuff, developing great code, interfaces that work, &amp;amp; systems that talk to each other. We have the ability to solve extremely complex business problems. To do that, RedMane hires &amp;amp; develops people who are passionate, brilliant, and who come to work every day looking for a new challenge to solve.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Relic Entertainment</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/relic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/relic/</guid>
      <description>Relic Entertainment, a wholly owned studio of SEGA, is the award winning RTS developer of Homeworld, Dawn of War and Company of Heroes, and we’re on the hunt for a Senior VFX Artist to work at our Vancouver studio. As a studio, our role is to create a workplace where people are energized and empowered to not only do their best work but to continually surpass their best. We’ll push you out of your comfort zone to become the best version of you by giving you the ownership and creative freedom to solve our most challenging problems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SAP</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/sap/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/sap/</guid>
      <description>SAP is the world’s leading provider of enterprise applications, cloud services, analytics, mobile, and database. SAP helps organizations fight the damaging effects of complexity, generate new opportunities for innovation and growth, and stay ahead of the competition.
From back office to boardroom, warehouse to storefront, desktop to mobile device, SAP empowers people and organizations to work together more efficiently and use business insight more effectively to stay ahead of the competition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SMART Technologies</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/smart-technologies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/smart-technologies/</guid>
      <description>SMART is changing the world by changing the way knowledge can be shared. Our software and hardware solutions empower everyone — from primary school students to innovators in Fortune 500 companies — to come together to explore and expand on ideas, bringing them to life without geographical or technological limitations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Safe Software</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/safe-software/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/safe-software/</guid>
      <description>The world is swamped in data, and organizations are feeling the pain. Our FME products reduce the friction and allow our thousands of (very happy) customers to painlessly move data from anywhere to everywhere. Whatever the type of data – be it sensors, maps, building models, imagery, databases, social media, web services, and more – FME is up for the task.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Samsung R&amp;D Canada</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/samsung/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/samsung/</guid>
      <description>Samsung R&amp;amp;D Canada is a part of Samsung Electronics Canada Ltd. Located in Barnaby, BC, Samsung R&amp;amp;D Canada is driven to build a culture of innovation that rapidly translates research and new ideas into the unexpected. We are making big steps into enterprise mobility, mobile payment and the Internet of Things (IoT) with a wide range of new devices and SW solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simba Technologies</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/simba/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/simba/</guid>
      <description>Simba Technologies, a wholly owned subsidiary of Magnitude Software, Inc., is the recognized world leader in standards-based data access and analytics products and solutions for relational and multi-dimensional data sources. Simba provides data connectivity solutions to many of the world’s leading companies on various platforms, including Windows, Mac, UNIX, Linux and mobile device platforms. Simba’s data connectivity products support multiple interfaces, including ODBC, JDBC, OLE DB, OLE DB for OLAP (ODBO), XML for Analysis (XMLA), ADO, ADO.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tableau</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/tableau/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/tableau/</guid>
      <description>Tableau Software is an American computer software company headquartered in Seattle, Washington. It produces a family of interactive data visualization products focused on business intelligence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tasktop Technologies</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/tasktop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/tasktop/</guid>
      <description>Over one million users employ Tasktop&amp;rsquo;s ALM and DevOps integration technology to transform the productivity of software delivery, by connecting the development, testing, Agile planning, PMO and operations functions into a unified software development and delivery team.
We are looking for highly-motivated individuals who have a passion for innovation and excellence as we help software development and delivery teams take their innovation to a new level.
Our culture emphasizes teamwork, openness, professional development, and quality of life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trader Corporation</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/trader-corporation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/trader-corporation/</guid>
      <description>autoTRADER.ca, a fast growing leader in the automotive industry, is one of Canada’s largest digital businesses, with unrivalled consumer and dealer brand recognition.
The cornerstone of our product universe is autoTRADER.ca, the leading new and used auto, truck and power sports classified site in Canada. Empowering Canadians to buy &amp;amp; sell like pro’s, leveraging both our 4.5 star rated mobile app, comparison features and car reviews. Through significant marketing investment autoTRADER.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vigilant</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/vigilant/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/vigilant/</guid>
      <description>Vigilant- a DRW Company is a Montreal-based R&amp;amp;D and IT firm that designs and deploys high-performance systems for the global financial markets.
Mission: Vigilant - a DRW Company creates state-of-the-art technology solutions for the world of electronic finance. To do that, we bring together bright minds, great ideas and industry leading tech in a work environment that inspires innovation. Vigilant invests in the communities where our employees live and work—giving back has been a core part of our business since day one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visier Inc</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/visier/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/visier/</guid>
      <description>A leading innovator in Applied Big Data cloud technology, Visier provides Workforce Intelligence solutions that are enabling a rapidly growing number of the world’s best brands to maximize their business outcomes through their people.
Founded by business intelligence experts—including former Business Objects chief executive officer, John Schwarz—the company’s leadership team has a proven track record of technical, operational, and strategic management success with companies such as IBM, SAP, and Oracle. With millions of customer employee records in the cloud, Visier is experiencing significant growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yelp</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/yelp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/yelp/</guid>
      <description>Yelp sees 89 million mobile users and 79 million desktop users every month. Keeping everything running smoothly requires the best and brightest in the industry. Our engineers come from diverse technical backgrounds and value digital craftsmanship, open­source, and creative problem solving. We write tests, review code, and push multiple times a day. From operations and infrastructure teams that handle scaling traffic and building a deployment platform, to backend and frontend teams that build features to enable users to find what they’re searching for, we have a talented group of extraordinary engineers that will help you grow and succeed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zenefits</title>
      <link>https://ubctcf.com/companies/zenefits/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubctcf.com/companies/zenefits/</guid>
      <description>Zenefits is the leading all-in-one Digital HR platform for small and medium businesses. Designed as the single source of truth for managing the modern workforce, Zenefits delivers the most complete, all-mobile HR experience by tightly integrating its own powerful applications with dozens of best-of-breed providers on the Zenefits platform. Zenefits’ applications like HR, Benefits, Time, Payroll and Compliance combine with partner applications like email, collaboration, expense management, and employee engagement to create a powerful platform.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>